<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GuHuDataInfo>
   <GuHuData post_ID="1">
      <Category_Name>Food</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>1</Display_Order>
      <Title>Antonio, Caff&amp;#233; Gambrinus</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;"I started here that I was eight, as a table boy. At the time, the area was said to be 'bella di giorno, brutta di notte' (    &lt;em&gt;nice at day, ugly at night&lt;/em&gt;). We would have all the noble men during the day, but by two in the morning we would be bringing coffees to the "pretty&#xD;    women" (i.e. prostitutes) that were just outsides here. Today, almost thirty years later, I have become head waiter here. Noble men and all tourists keep&#xD;    on coming and everyone knows about this very famous Neapolitan bar, probably the best known bar in Naples."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Can you tell me something a tourist does not know about this place?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "I doubt it they know that the very first coffee here was made with a machine from Milano. Today, however, they come from Milano to learn how to make our&#xD;    coffee."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Food #PiazzaDelPlebiscito #CaffeGambrinus #TableBoy #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T1P1.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>http://grancaffegambrinus.com/en</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Caff%C3%A8_Gambrinus,_Naples</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g187785-d1091714-Reviews-Gran_Caffe_Gambrinus-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.83700</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24854</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="2">
      <Category_Name>Food</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>2</Display_Order>
      <Title>Mimmo, pescheria Azzurra</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;"My father opened this fish shop in 1947, giving it the same name as the colour of the sea, Azzurro. The fish market itself had already the name it bears&#xD;    today, &lt;em&gt;il mercato della Pignasecca&lt;/em&gt;. My son is continuing our tradition for the third generation. We still supply prestigious restaurants and&#xD;    hotels, but things have changed a lot for this centennial market.&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    We are trying to protect this place. Recently, we managed to convince the district and the mayor that mopeds and vehicles should not transit here, and have&#xD;    it only for pedestrians instead. It had such an impact on this market, because the&lt;em&gt; Pignasecca&lt;/em&gt; is our story too."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Do you know why it is called this way? It is because of an old pine tree that used to be right in the centre of the square. The tree exsiccated, and so&#xD;    were its pine cones, hence Pigna (&lt;em&gt;pine cone&lt;/em&gt;) secca (&lt;em&gt;dry&lt;/em&gt;). Since pine trees are protected in this area, it survived long enough to give a&#xD;    name to this market. The story of Naples is in its markets and its streets."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Food #FishShop #Pignasecca #Mercato #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T1P2.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>https://www.facebook.com/pages/Pescheria-Azzurra/230021133681329</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>http://www.agrodolce.it/2015/08/05/migliori-pescherie-napoli/</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.yelp.com/biz_photos/pescheria-azzurra-napoli?select=1ZztaGXXlSKuOLKw6fL4CA</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84584</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24810</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="3">
      <Category_Name>Food</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>3</Display_Order>
      <Title>Ciro, pasticceria Poppella</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;"We have been here for ten years now, at the heart of one of the oldest and most popular neighbours in Napoli. We wouldn't be here if we didn't put passion&#xD;    in what we do. Every sweet we make, every cake, every &lt;em&gt;sfogliatella&lt;/em&gt; we make comes from us putting in our very best. Will then it be served on&#xD;    tables where noble men sit, or will it be eaten just outside our &lt;em&gt;pasticceria&lt;/em&gt; for a small change, it doesn't matter to us. Another important&#xD;    ingredient in our job is creativity. You wouldn't guess it, but the new product they ask us more and more is one we came up with only two years ago. It&#xD;    also has an atypical name for this city: "fiocchi di neve" (&lt;em&gt;snowflakes&lt;/em&gt;). It is a combination of &lt;em&gt;tradition&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;creativity&lt;/em&gt;.&#xD;    Tradition is where we started from: even the name of the shop, "poppella", actually comes from five evolutions of my gran-mother's first name (Giuseppina,&#xD;    then Peppina, Peppiniella and finally Poppella). Creativity, instead, is our &lt;em&gt;snowflakes&lt;/em&gt;. It works so well it even snowed this year!"&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Food #Pasticceria #SnowFlakes #TraditionAndInnovation #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T1P3.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>https://www.facebook.com/Pasticceria-Poppella-350973065087920/</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>http://www.yelp.com/biz/pasticceria-ciro-poppella-napoli</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g187785-d6404369-Reviews-Pasticceria_Poppella-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.85774</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25302</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="4">
      <Category_Name>Food</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>4</Display_Order>
      <Title>Signora Carmela</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "I have been here for 54 years, my father opened the first kiosk in front of the San Carlo theatre. Times have changed since then, it was always better&#xD;    before! When we moved our shop to this area, 'ai Tribunali, next to me was Zia Esterina (&lt;em&gt;now called Pizzeria Sorbillo&lt;/em&gt;) with her pizzeria with just&#xD;    four tables. What a woman she was! She worked all day without rest, but at the end of the day she always had the energy to scold all her employees! But the&#xD;    pizzas there&amp;#8230;the best &lt;em&gt;pizza fritta&lt;/em&gt; you could eat in Napoli!"&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "For me, I sell small grocery, and here most tourists would only stop for sodas. But if you ask me, they should drink fresh juice instead. We have the best&#xD;    lemon and orange fruits in the world.&#xD;    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Signorina, do you want to try?"&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Food #Grocery #ZiaEsterina #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T1P4.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link/>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.85226</latitude>
         <longitude>14.26040</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="5">
      <Category_Name>Food</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>5</Display_Order>
      <Title>Giovanni, Spiedo D'Oro</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Sometimes I feel like a desert island, like a lighthouse that tries to illuminate a no man's land. We have been in this very place for 24 years, but I&#xD;    started this job 42 years ago with my dad. He was a cook. He thought me many things. I understood what it means to work with passion and always giving&#xD;    one's very best. Before there was a lot more humanity, compassion, perhaps because we were all poorer. At the beginning of the 80's, many of the jobs in&#xD;    this area were based on loving relationships between people. We invented everything to overcome hunger. I remember there was the "arriffatore": a man&#xD;    selling made-up lottery numbers. After the sale, he would come back screaming the winning numbers he would pick from a wicker basket. For every number, he&#xD;    would act and improvise a show, and there were five winning numbers accompanied by dances and songs. A little bit like a modern bingo. We should try not to&#xD;    forget our past."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Food #Restaurant #WeShouldntForgetThe #arriffatore #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T1P5.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>https://www.facebook.com/Spiedo-dOro-Trattoria-817340008293197/</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g187785-d2510300-Reviews-Spiedo_d_Oro-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84580</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24747</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="6">
      <Category_Name>Food</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>6</Display_Order>
      <Title>Piero, pizzeria Di Matteo</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;How long have you been working here?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Be understanding, Signorina, I see you want to chat. But if you want to chat you should go to Salvatore, the manager&amp;#8230;we only make pizzas. Do you&#xD;    like the pizza we make?"&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Well, yes.&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "See, this is our story."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Food #Pizzeria #Tribunali #Our Story #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T1P6.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>http://www.pizzeriadimatteo.com/</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g187785-d801210-Reviews-Antica_Pizzeria_e_Friggitoria_Di_Matteo-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.85123</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25802</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="7">
      <Category_Name>Food</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>7</Display_Order>
      <Title>Salvatore, Friggitoria Vomero</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;"Any good, ma'am?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    I have been preparing these every day for 30 years, sticking to the tradition as much as possible; for instance, leaving them to rise overnight. Little
    things like this make this place unique. The owners were very brave to open this shop in 1938, between the two wars, and to this day this is the only
    venue.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    With the cable car stopping not far from here, there is a large flow of people, also from the low side of Naples, and this helps us to be always at full
    capacity ... This has taught me over the years to get up to 80 croquettes per minute if necessary. I am not even sure how many that makes a day.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    If you want to learn how to make the real Neapolitan "fritto" (&lt;em&gt;frying&lt;/em&gt;), this city can be a school. But young people do not seem interested
    anymore, an education may be a better choice for them; so they say. I have a son graduated in Rome in nursing and now he's unemployed. So I wonder what is
    there for these young men?
    &lt;br/&gt;
It used to be that finding a job would have set you on the right path, even "saved" your life. At least, it was the case for me. Coming from the Sanita' (    &lt;em&gt;neighbour in Naples&lt;/em&gt;), it was not easy, but thanks to this fry shop I could leave the ghetto. And now? I am teaching my craft to the kids in of
    this neighbourhood, as I can. It's a chance they have and I treat them as if they were my children. They are our resources for a better future."
&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T1P7.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;rlz=1C1KMZB_enGB570GB570&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=friggitoria+vomero+naples</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>http://www.lonelyplanet.com/italy/campania/naples/restaurants/fast-food/friggitoria-vomero</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g187785-d1091757-Reviews-Friggitoria_Vomero-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84290</latitude>
         <longitude>14.23279</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="8">
      <Category_Name>Shop</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>1</Display_Order>
      <Title>Fulvio Forte</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Where am I from? I was born 100 meters down this road, and got married 100 meters up this road, where that Church is, can you see it? I took on the job of&#xD;    my father, much like my father did with his father, and so on as it was done for about four generations before me. Our family has been around from mid&#xD;    800's.&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    It isn't easy to keep traditions intact, but many people still come to San Gregorio Armeno to make their &lt;em&gt;Presepe&lt;/em&gt; like they used to do even&#xD;    hundreds years ago. We owe it to them and to those who preceded us to preserve our art.&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    This is despite the fact that national and international media always depict Naples as a place of criminality and garbage. Sure, we have our issues, who&#xD;    doesn't, but there is so much more here for those who want to see."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;This is not helping sales, I imagine..&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "It isn't, but I like to say that "while it's never been worse, every year it's getting better."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #FulvioForte #Shop #GregorioArmeno #Presepe #StayPositive #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T2P1.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link/>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.85000</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25806</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="9">
      <Category_Name>Shop</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>2</Display_Order>
      <Title>Street Flower shop</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Him&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;    : It's 1&amp;#8364; a bouquet.&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Woman:&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;    Can you believe, I paid &amp;#8364;8 for a bouquet like this in Rome the other day.&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Him again, after some brief pondering&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;    :&#xD;    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;    ...&#xD;    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;    I can sell you two bouquets &amp;#8364;8 euro then?&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;(joking, maybe.)&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Street #Shop #PiazzaDelGesu #Florist #quickComeback #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T2P2.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Church_of_the_Ges%C3%B9</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d6681586-Reviews-Piazza_del_Gesu_Nuovo-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84716</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25187</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="10">
      <Category_Name>Shop</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>3</Display_Order>
      <Title>Giuseppe, Loveri music shop</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "The story of my shop is one of pride and glory, up to a point, at least.&#xD;    &lt;br/&gt;&#xD;    I think of what my dad was able to do, and I doubt every day I'd be able to replicate it. During the Second World War he was one of the first that tried&#xD;    building and selling drums that, in the meantime, had become famous after the American had brought jazz into our culture. My dad could afford to buy an&#xD;    apartment for himself and he could look after his three children and their families. We never went without. But his biggest contribution was towards this&#xD;    city, having finally turned San Sebastiano into the "strad e' musicist" (street of musicians), which is how locals call this area of Napoli. He wasn't the&#xD;    only to start this process: other families, and for at least two generations after him, joined the effort and some still have their music instrument shops&#xD;    up and down this road. Now you understand why I am sad that all this may not last much longer."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Is this street bound to disappear?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "I can't say it for sure. Napoli is evolving fast. Do you see the shop that is just in front of us, now closed? Yesterday it used to be one of the best&#xD;    known music and instrument shop. Tomorrow is going to be a fries shop, maybe."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;What is the biggest privilege of your work?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Being part of someone's discovery of music and, sometimes, of their talent. You see a boy buying a drum, one day. Then you see the same guy coming back,&#xD;getting a better instrument, or performing with us. I can't tell you how many musician this street has seen. In a way, it is still a gift from the    &lt;em&gt;strad 'e musicist&lt;/em&gt; that keeps on giving."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Shops #Loveri #Music #Instruments #viaSanSebastiano #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T2P3.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link>http://www.loveri.com</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link/>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84927</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25207</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="11">
      <Category_Name>Shop</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>4</Display_Order>
      <Title>Raffaele, librarian in Piazza Dante</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Vita mia, e' morte tua! (&lt;em&gt;my wellbeing is your disgrace - literally, death&lt;/em&gt;)."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T2P4.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link/>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84928</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25052</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="12">
      <Category_Name>Shop</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>5</Display_Order>
      <Title>Mr. Marinella (ties shop) and his secretary</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    Mr. Marinella: "Good evening. Would you be so kind as to arrange an appointment with my secretary for next week?"&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Sure, Ok.&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    Would Monday work for you?&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Yes&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    Great. Actually, we'll do the interview via telephone, but I am afraid it will be with me. Mr. Marinella is very busy on Mondays.&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Shops #Marinella #Busy #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T2P5.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>http://www.marinellanapoli.it/en/index.php</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/E._Marinella</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d4740659-Reviews-Marinella-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.83344</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24080</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="13">
      <Category_Name>Shop</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>6</Display_Order>
      <Title>Mario, Talarico Ombrelli</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "L'omm adda fa l'omm! (A man's gotta be a man). I have been sitting behind this desk for 72 years, which by the way is 203 years old itself, and I have&#xD;    been working every day, 13 hours a day. Money is important, but you have to stay humble or it will turn even family into enemies. In fact, one of the&#xD;    fortunes in my life is the fact that I had my nephew, my "arm", Mario Jr. by my side: he is very talented, with loads of passion and creativity. He's&#xD;    followed my footsteps and once I am gone, he will be in charge of the business. Together we make art pieces that are known everywhere, and that have&#xD;    allowed me to travel around the world. I have reached the peak of my life, and from there I saw the most beautiful scenery."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;What made you come down from there?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Even though many very important people wear the hats and umbrellas I've made for them, my origins keep me humble. My shop reflects this: in the front&#xD;    window there are umbrellas that are very expensive, and others that are not worth much one next to the other. One time the ambassador of England was&#xD;    looking for my shop on Toledo Street. But once outside, he hesitated to come in because of those umbrellas, too cheap to be in the shop he had heard so&#xD;    much about&amp;#8230; he thought he had come to the wrong place! Later, enthusiastic about my work, he asked me if I would come over to his house for a photo&#xD;    of the three of us: myself, the ambassador, and the umbrella of course."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Shop #Umbrellas #Talarico #ViaToledo #StayHumble #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T2P6.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>http://www.mariotalarico.it/</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://www.facebook.com/Mario-Talarico-Ombrelli-da-Sempre-111698705561047/</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;rlz=1C1KMZB_enGB570GB570&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=talarico%20ombrelli%20napoli&amp;lrd=0x133b085ae2efa04f:0x2c4b1efbd3deac23,1</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84572</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24908</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="14">
      <Category_Name>Shop</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>7</Display_Order>
      <Title>Lucio Ferrigno, embellishments</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "I'm a criminal lawyer. You may wonder what I am doing in a shop that sells hand-made art pieces for &lt;em&gt;presepe&lt;/em&gt; and embellishments. One day my father&#xD;    asked me to cover his shift at the shop he was working for at that time, the very same shop you see now. It was a beautiful day and my first day on the job&#xD;    I have enjoyed over the following 35 years. Ever since, I have been searching for beauty in objects rather than in people. In people I look at their hidden&#xD;    aspects, their dark side. When I am working at one of my hand-made pieces, black is the colour I prefer, but my shop is full of colours much like the city&#xD;    we live in. When it's sunny, Napoli appears as every postcard would depict it; but come back at night, and you'll see these same streets turn into a&#xD;    painting by Caravaggio, with dark and enchanting sides."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;If you had to choose a colour for Napoli, what would it be?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Black, again, like the colour of piperno (&lt;em&gt;the material used for pavement&lt;/em&gt;). It's under our feet every day in the streets of this city and it&#xD;    reminds us of the burning lava it was created from, and the hell Naples can turn into. Then, as one looks up at the spectacles of a clear bluer sky, the&#xD;    thousands of colours appear again."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Shop #FioriFinti #SanGregorioArmeno #piperno #presepe #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T2P7.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link>www.arteferrigno.i</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d5523556-Reviews-Ferrigno_Lucio-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84927</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25207</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="15">
      <Category_Name>Shop</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>8</Display_Order>
      <Title>Raffaella, Fonoteca</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;"It's not that long ago I started working here. I used to work in a bar, and then the passion for music led me to sell CDs and vinyl. We cover a lot of
    different stuff, for customers that are eclectic and affectionate. There is the boy with the monthly pocket money buying a CD of Clementino, and there is
    the expert in classical music that maybe wants to buy a vinyl for 35 Euros. But my favourite type of customers is the tourist. The often stop by this shop
    on their way to San Martino, and on the way back they want a Vinyl or CD of Neapolitan music. And I understand it all because I have been that tourist 15
    years ago, when I moved from Venezuela. I could not have chosen any other Italian place. Naples and its many colours remind me of my mother land: Caracas,
    chaotic, full of contrasts and with a profound Latin soul. I feel at home."
&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T2P8.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>https://www.facebook.com/fonotecanapoli/</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;rlz=1C1KMZB_enGB570GB570&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=fonoteca+vomero+naples&amp;lrd=0x133b08f986e43191:0x72ffe611b470fec,1</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g187785-d8806179-Reviews-Fonoteca-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84333</latitude>
         <longitude>14.23381</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="16">
      <Category_Name>Views</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>1</Display_Order>
      <Title>Cataldo, guardian of the Maschio Angioino</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "The first day I stepped into the Maschio Angioino it was hugely emotional. But I had no idea at the time that I would have become its guardian one day,&#xD;    and for over thirty years now. I was what you would call a &lt;em&gt;scugnizzo&lt;/em&gt;, a street boy. I didn't have a job and I was angry, but I decided not to keep&#xD;    it in. And I wasn't alone: with me, there was a group of thirty people that soon became trouble, a burden the governors did not want to have. So one day&#xD;    they phoned me up and offered me this job."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Has your job changed you?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "More than anything! More than the week I spent behind the bars. This is my home now: at times I wander around and I could take you to the corners of this&#xD;    fortress that nobody knows. Art has taught me a lot. Don't get me wrong, I am still hopeless when it comes to learning from books, but I have learned to&#xD;    observe and respect the beautiful forms of art that Napoli has."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Naples #Views #MaschioAngioino #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T3P1.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;rlz=1C1KMZB_enGB570GB570&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=maschio%20angioino%20napoli&amp;lrd=0x133b084e6e5d6497:0xc131a1902329c922,1</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Castel_Nuovo</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d243322-Reviews-Castel_Nuovo_Maschio_Angioino-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.83836</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25361</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="17">
      <Category_Name>Views</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>2</Display_Order>
      <Title>Antonella, Cappella San Severo</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "I have been working here for 15 years, every day seems my first. Watching the &lt;em&gt;Cristo Velato&lt;/em&gt; still shakes me. I didn't choose to be here because&#xD;    of religion. It was by chance, actually: I started off in the ticket office, then a position opened where I could be closer to people and the art. Every&#xD;    day I observe a lot of people come and go, and many, once in front of this wonderful statue, burst into tears. It is as if it could bring out everything we&#xD;    have in the deepest part of us, as if such beauty could disarm us."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Sometimes I look at &lt;em&gt;Cristo Velato&lt;/em&gt; and it seems to me that breaths: an agony halted by one last breath. It is so powerful, that explains why there&#xD;    are so many legends about it. The &lt;em&gt;prince of San Severo&lt;/em&gt; was considered an alchemist, so it was believed that he could send the curses. One of these&#xD;    curses, people believed, was addressed to those who did not have a school degree: people believed that if you didn't have one, it would be bad luck for you&#xD;    to enter the cappella. Knowing how Neapolitan are superstitious, imagine how many never visited it!"&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Then, a visitor decides to join the conversation:&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "In fact, this is where you should take children to teach the difference between beautiful and ugly, to let them know the greatness of art! Not the&#xD;    Maldives with coconuts: there have nice beaches, but the real beauty is another thing. Art is the only thing that can arouse emotions while standing still&#xD;    for hours, staring at a masterpiece and travelling far with the mind at the same time."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Views #CappellaSanSevero #CristoVelato #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T3P2.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>http://www.museosansevero.it/en/</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cappella_Sansevero</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d195631-Reviews-Museo_Cappella_Sansevero-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84953</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25485</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="18">
      <Category_Name>Views</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>3</Display_Order>
      <Title>Orazio, Duomo</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;"San gennaro &amp;#232; &amp;#242; spion r&amp;#242; Padreterno! (&lt;em&gt;San Gennaro is the informer of God&lt;/em&gt;!).
    &lt;br/&gt;
    So Neapolitans define our patron saint and there you can understand their deep devotion. The Duomo, as well as being one of the most important churches of
    our city, is unique in a way not everyone knows. While being very big at the naked eye, only the central hall really belongs to the church, whereas the
    right side is the chapel of San Gennaro, and the left one is the Santa Restituta, and both used to belong to other bodies. This is an anomaly so typical of
    Naples: a so close coexistence of Church and State. And being so close, isn't always easy: although there is a great mutual respect (not celebrated the
    same times, in procession politicians are forward all etc ...), the Church does not share fully the choices of the Chapel of the Patron. Having to pay to
    visit the area dedicated to OUR patron is unacceptable to us, these are assets that belong to the people of this city!"
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;San Gennaro is also important in the world for the liquefaction of the blood, but it's a real miracle ?&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    "Absolutely yes! &lt;em&gt;San Gennaro&lt;/em&gt; makes the miracle twice a year: in September for the Neapolitans and in May for the rest of the world. He is speaking
    to his people. He always announced disaster when not dissolved the blood. Just think of the earthquake that happened last time that the miracle did not
    take place, in the 1973..."
&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T3P3.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;rlz=1C1KMZB_enGB570GB570&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=duomo+napoli&amp;lrd=0x133b086a71dc7939:0x8bad90ad52187adc,1</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Naples_Cathedral</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d1987333-Reviews-Duomo_di_Napoli-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.85253</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25960</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="19">
      <Category_Name>Views</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>4</Display_Order>
      <Title>Castel Sant'Elmo</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    Not collected yet.&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T3P4.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;rlz=1C1KMZB_enGB570GB570&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=castel+sant%27elmo+naples&amp;lrd=0x133b086b48581d91:0x2e60ca1f420ca73c,1</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Castel_Sant%27Elmo</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d604735-Reviews-Castel_Sant_Elmo-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84385</latitude>
         <longitude>14.23924</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="20">
      <Category_Name>Fun</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>1</Display_Order>
      <Title>Mario, Teatro San Carlo</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "I worked for almost thirty years in theaters all around Italy, but this is my home now. There is something special about this thaeter that you don't find&#xD;    anywhere else, believe me. At night, before a show, you can tell that people of different backgrounds and class meet, even though they stay separate in the&#xD;    place the sit. From the third row of stalls, and the balconies, you can find noble men and those that hold year tickets. Then below there are those that&#xD;    are occasional and down in the hall there are middle class people, and students sometimes."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;What about the poorest?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Those do the job I do!" (&lt;em&gt;he smiles&lt;/em&gt;)&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Fund #TeatroSanCarlo #Theatre #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T4P1.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>http://www.teatrosancarlo.it/</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Teatro_di_San_Carlo</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d195418-Reviews-Teatro_di_San_Carlo-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.83756</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24964</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="21">
      <Category_Name>Fun</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>2</Display_Order>
      <Title>Antonella, Qualcosa di t&amp;#233;</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "My husband and I opened this shop 5 years ago. The idea came after a trip to Istanbul. There you have tea served at every occasion and in every street. We&#xD;    thought that something like this was missing in Napoli, so we did it. At first we chose &lt;em&gt;Spaccanapoli&lt;/em&gt; area for our shop, right at the heart of the&#xD;    city, and we liked it: there were artisans and shops with a deep history and traditions. After all, even if you're trying to do something new it doesn't&#xD;    mean you have to give up your origins. But with time, the area started to turn into an open-air shopping mall, selling really impersonal stuff, so we&#xD;    relocated here. It's only 100 meters down the road, but those iron stakes make you really feel the difference. We couldn't be happier now. We've even&#xD;    managed to convince our friends to open a tea room just across from our shop."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;How did you make Napoli find room for tea?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "This city is more open to new things than what many think. Thanks to tourists and Neapolitans that stop by our shop every day, the business is going well&#xD;    and we're thinking to get even more tea shops! We also thought about providing coffee as well, but the exploitation behind its production put us off a&#xD;    little. We respect other people's work, as we expect it other people to respect ours."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Food #Tea #Respect #QualcosaDiTe #Naples #GuHu #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T4P2.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link>https://www.facebook.com/Qualcosadite-il-primo-tea-shop-Partenopeo-183949008334381/</Wikipedia_Link>
      <Google1_Link>https://www.google.com/webhp?sourceid=chrome-instant&amp;rlz=1C1KMZB_enGB570GB570&amp;ion=1&amp;espv=2&amp;ie=UTF-8#q=qualcosa+di+te+naples&amp;lrd=0x133b0843c36f8297:0xc0629b3c96df816f,1</Google1_Link>
      <Google2_Link/>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84873</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25623</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="22">
      <Category_Name>Fun</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>3</Display_Order>
      <Title>Armando, Cammarota Spritz Bar</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "I've been here for ten years. Every day I relate with people from all over the world and from all walks. Each taught me something: tourists, students,&#xD;    drunkards... and also the ignorant! I grew up on the street, and I realized that in life you have to make many sacrifices to get somewhere. Eventually,&#xD;    also with a little 'luck, say 5%, you can get where you want. &lt;em&gt;A 'ciort&lt;/em&gt; (good luck) is important in life, but that's not all! When I opened this&#xD;    shop, it was a cellar pleasing few drunkards at best. &lt;em&gt;O 'Baron&lt;/em&gt; ("the baron") was one of them. A man who is in many stories about Naples. He spent&#xD;    most of his life drunk, but he knew how to tell and convey the emotions of a life lived to the fullest, and often also painful."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "In these streets I also met my wife, who gave me a son. She is Scottish in origins and habits: thanks to her I learned things such as order and&#xD;    concreteness. It was her that when one day the sewer system collapsed in the building, instead of complying with my idea to shut down, she made me get up&#xD;    on my feet and rebuild the shop, allowing me to continue believing in this project. A project that started as a little thing, making the first "spritz" of&#xD;    Naples to make&amp;#8230; drinkers drink more!&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    Today is still standing, one of the places best known of the &lt;em&gt;Quartieri Spagnoli&lt;/em&gt;, for our spritz and more!"&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Cammarota #Fun #CentroStorico #Drink #Spritz #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T4P3.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d6164379-Reviews-Cammarota_Spritz-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.84211</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24725</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="23">
      <Category_Name>People</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>1</Display_Order>
      <Title>Street sweeper</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "See, we have a problem with taking pictures. The problem is that you'll post it on a journal, tomorrow or the day after, and then everyone says, "oh&#xD;    that's another sweeper that is not working!"&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;What if I take a photo of you holding the broom then?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "That we can do. Am I looking good?"&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #StreetSweeper #CentroStorico # viaDeiTribunali #LookingGood #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T5P1.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d1482716-Reviews-Via_dei_Tribunali-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.85115</latitude>
         <longitude>14.25735</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="24">
      <Category_Name>People</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>2</Display_Order>
      <Title>Pedlar in Via Toledo</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "There is no magic".&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #StreetPedlar #ViaToledo #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T5P2.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d2540374-Reviews-Via_Toledo-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.82838</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24847</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="25">
      <Category_Name>People</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>3</Display_Order>
      <Title>Street sweeper part II</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;   "Are you still here??"&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Naples #People #Street&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T5P3.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d1482716-Reviews-Via_dei_Tribunali-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.83601</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24831</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="26">
      <Category_Name>People</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>4</Display_Order>
      <Title>Antonio, stampe antiche</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "You need to be a branch of this tree to understand this city. Many, who are not, tend to be diffident. What you hear about us do not make us any favour,&#xD;    but luckily Neapolitans put up with it. We are proud of our land. I've worked here since the '90s. I grew up on the street and the street has taught me how&#xD;    to live. My father passed this job onto me. We started with photographs, and after we moved on to prints in black and white, and now I sell colour prints&#xD;    of the nineteenth century. I try to raise awareness of the beauty that does not change. This city is gold! You only really understand its value if you were&#xD;    born here."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Will tourists ever be able to understand it?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "It depends on the tourist, but there is one thing that does make a difference: if you're coming to Napoli, you have to come curious, not fearful. Wanting&#xD;    to &lt;em&gt;live&lt;/em&gt; the city more than wanting to &lt;em&gt;visit&lt;/em&gt; it. Each passing day I see tourists from all nationalities and despite the fact that I&#xD;    haven't studied a lot, I can relate to them in a natural way. They are part of this city, much like I am part of it."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Shop #Printings #CuriousNotFearful #PiazzaDelPlebiscito #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T5P4.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link/>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.83664</latitude>
         <longitude>14.24858</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
   <GuHuData post_ID="27">
      <Category_Name>People</Category_Name>
      <Display_Order>5</Display_Order>
      <Title>Stranger in front of a strange shop</Title>
      <Description_Text>&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;A man standing outside the shop 'Ospedale delle Bambole':&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "It's closed! You should go to their laboratory, but I am not sure you'd find anybody there either."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;But here on the sign it says they are just down the road? &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "I know, but sometimes they come to work, some other times they don't."&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    &lt;em&gt;Then why would the lights be on?&lt;/em&gt;&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    "Eh, they're a bit messed up!"&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;&#xD;&lt;p&gt;&#xD;    #GuHu #Shop #Dolls #Confused #Naples&#xD;&lt;/p&gt;</Description_Text>
      <Photo>/photo/shop/T5P5.jpg</Photo>
      <Wikipedia_Link/>
      <Google1_Link/>
      <Google2_Link>http://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g187785-d7988556-Reviews-Ospedale_delle_bambole-Naples_Province_of_Naples_Campania.html</Google2_Link>
      <Geo_Map_Coordinates>
         <latitude>40.85001</latitude>
         <longitude>14.26014</longitude>
      </Geo_Map_Coordinates>
   </GuHuData>
</GuHuDataInfo>